Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Living Stage Theater Company records, 1966-2000; 36 linear ft. (68 boxes)
  - Roosevelt Senior center program (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Amazing Life Games 2-4's (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Amazing Life Games 5-7's (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Misc. performance pieces (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ballou High School (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Foundry program (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Wakefield P.S. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - One Shots (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - JAMS (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Fairhill (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Personnel (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - 1982 fund raiser letter (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - 1982 working letters (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - DC Commission on the Arts grants, samples and forms (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - December public performance 1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Workshop fund raising letter 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - public performance events (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Leland (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Sandi (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - misc. benefit information (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - January 31, 1983 fund letter (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - February Fund Drive (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Canaide (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Benefit 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - newsletters 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - newsletter (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Spring Newsletter 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - newsletter (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - newsletter, winter 1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter spring 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - corporate lunch (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - corporate seminar (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Bldg. press conference (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - new building press (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Living Stage: press releases (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - volunteer packages (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - originals (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - direct mail program (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - misc. printed PR pieces (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - production info (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - public performance, May 9, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage letters (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - short term plan (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - St. Lukes Benefit (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - RA DAY (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Renwick 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - newsletters 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Living Stage acquisition/artwork 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - residency evaluations (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Living Stage PR (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - 1989 London/Paris tour (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - clean-up and misc. projects (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage FY 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - LS benefit 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage committee (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Living Stage general information (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage article process (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Living Stage: 1988-1989 season evaluations (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Living Stage committee meetings 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sugar Ray Leonard (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - letter shop (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - pictures (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Arena Stage for Children and Youth 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage 1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - 1973-1974 production reports (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 1973-1974 production reports (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Lead Sheets 1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Production reports 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 1977-1978 performance report (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - performance report 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Franklin Sherman production notes 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - production reports 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - production reports and jams 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - production reports 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - production reports 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1982-1983 production reports (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1983-1984 season reports (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1983-1984 performance reports (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1983-1984 performance reports (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - rehearsal notes 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The Crystal Chapter (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Crystal Chapter (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - production reports: 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - reheal reports: 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - production reports: 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - production reports: 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - production reports: 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - production reports: 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - production reports: 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - residency session notes: 1987-1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - residency session notes: 1987-1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - residency session notes: 1987-1993 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - residency session notes: 1987-1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - I Had a Dream: group notes and evaluations 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - production reports: 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - production reports: 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - performance reports:1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - performance reports: 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 1992 west coast residency (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - teen mom productions:1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - I Had: production reports 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - scripts; 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - photos; misc. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - labeled photos; 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Living Stage jams: 1973-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage jams: 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - production reports: 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage handbook: 2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - production reports: 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Lynched Hopes and Unsung Dreams: photos 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - rehearsal photos: 1986-1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - photocopies of labeled photos (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - photocopies of theater tickets (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - photos: 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - photos from long street: 1986 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 1986-1987 performances (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1986-1987 performances (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1986-1987 performances (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 1986-1987 performances (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 1967-1970 press releases: New Orleans Workshop (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Press Releases 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - press releases 1967-1970: TV and Radio spots for children plays (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - press releases 1967-1970: Children theater 1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - press releases 1967-1970: curriculum enrichment (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - press releases 1967-1970: tri-school programs 1967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Robert Alexander's speaking engagements (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Children's Caravan (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Living Stage; notes, memos and oral correspondence (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Treasury Island Articles (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Danny Dither", author visit to Arena Stage (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Chuckle Dust Caper (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage Correspondence: 1968 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - misc. Living Stage 1971 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - copies of contracts: 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - misc. Living Stage correspondence: 1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - misc. Living Stage notes, memos, correspondence (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Old Biographies (prior to 1973) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Living Stage info: 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Ned Chaillet article: 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Living Stage company list: 1970's-1980's (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Living Stage company: 1970's-1980's (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Living Stage company: 1970's-1980's (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Living Stage company 1970's-1980's (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Living Stage Company: 1970's-1980's (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Life magazine: May 1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Photos (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - newspapers: misc. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage: bundle (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Children Theater and notes (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage and Chuckledust photos: 1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Living Stage, Treasury Island photos: 1961 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Social Program correspondence 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Fan Mail - School program (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - prints, records for tri-school 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - newspaper articles (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - memos; misc. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Living Stage photos; 1970's-1980's (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - The White House (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - The National Committee Arts for the handicapped (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - expense records - living stage - curriculum - enrichment program (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - correspondence on Boo's European Trip; 1968 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Danny Dither correspondence (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Wind in the Willows; response letters (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Wind in the Willows; correspondence (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Wind in the Willows; correspondence (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Living Stage correspondence; 1967 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - press releases; 1967-1970: Living Stage 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - misc. information (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - press releases 1967-1970: Living Stage 1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage misc. article; resources and references (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - misc. magazines (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - misc. magazines (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - photos (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - photos (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Robert Alexander (plays,poems) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Living Stage photos 1961; Danny Dither photos (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Wind and the Willows photos (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Wind in the Willows book (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Robert Alexander photos (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Improvisational Workshop Photos (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage photos (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Living Stage scrapbook (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Children Theater Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Children Theater Programs (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Children Theater Program (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Children Theater response letters (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Children Theaters Program: 1968 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Living Stage 1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage Articles; 1967-1981 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - response letters from non-residencies 1968-1992 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - response letters from season performance groups 1967-1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - response letters from residencies 1990-1992 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - response letters from residencies 1990-1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Inter generational project (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - National Bank proposal; Police Association, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Hasbro proposal report, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities FY 1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Poems and Songs for "Lynched Hopes" (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - proposal to W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Burton Bettingen Corp. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Earned Income; 1991 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - teen mother proposal; 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - ADASA 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - ADASA invoices 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - CSAP budget (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - CSAP activities 1995 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - CSAP APP 1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - federal assistance application (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - ADASA (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - ADASA 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - ADASA prevention contract; original proposal 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - ADASA prevention contract; original proposal 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - ADASA 1987 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - ADASA (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - ADASA 1990-1993 budget (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - CSAP conference (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - teen moms (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - teen mother project fact sheet (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - landmarks of Living Stage 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax proposal and response letters; 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Pieces 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - 1991-1992 fact sheet (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - ASP 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Media Material (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Artistic Statement from Robert Alexander; 1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Living Stage long range plan; 1992 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - 1990-1991 misc. season info (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - "I Had" evaluations 1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Workshops II (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Workshops IV 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - workshop III (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - workshops 1974; V (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - workshops 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - summer workshops 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - workshops 1982 VIII (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - summer workshops; 1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - summer workshops 1989 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - summer 1990 workshops (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - summer workshops 1994 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - summer workshop 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - All Power to the Imagination; brochure (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - booking now brochure (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Dear Martha Fund raiser (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - old fund raisers (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - I Know Another Way (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Let There be a New World (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Appendage to Theater Games (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - L.S. contacts 70 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - long range planning (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Hew End of the year Report 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Sharpe Health Grant app. 1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Fairfax (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - New Spirit Living Stage 14 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - L.S. Board Committee 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Building Committee Mtg. 1988 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Budget accounts 1981-1984 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - accounts 1966-1979 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - fund raising 1970-1980 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - management and goals 1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - foundations 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - foundations 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - foundations 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - foundations 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - foundations 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - foundations 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - foundations 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - foundations 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - budget 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - benefit (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Living Stage PR 1984 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - press kit; company resumes, Robert Alexander resume 1985 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - foundations 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - foundations 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - foundations 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - foundations 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - foundations 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - foundations 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Ford grant (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Robert Alexander's Christmas Cards 1986-1993 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - end of season info (1989-1990) (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - benefit general 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - benefits 1990 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Living Stage Benefit April 22, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Living Stage 25th Anniversary (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Children Defense Fund 1991 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - T.C.G. 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Moscow-DC capital citizens exchange, March 1987 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - I.H.A.D. 1989 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - residencies (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Living Stage Jams 1978-1981 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Breakfast 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Living Stage Jams 1973-1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Board Committee meetings information (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Board Committee meeting information (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage Correspondence 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Board Committee correspondence (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Artists Alliance for Prevention (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Living Stage Benefit 1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Space (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - T-Street Dossier (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Living Stage school (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Chicago residency Transcripts; 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Cleveland residency (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Atlanta/Detroit residency info and support letters 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore archive images 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Detroit 1987-1988 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Residency 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Residency 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - teen mom letters/fact sheet/ schedule (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - workshops 1978-1981 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - ADASA: monthly reports 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Ballou High School - 1989 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Summer Workshops 1990 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Summer Workshops 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - special education grant 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Orthopedic Continuation proposal 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - D.O.E. budget letter and letters of support (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - NEA special constituent grant final report (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage articles 1982-1988 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Living Stage articles 1982-1988 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Themes for age groups (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 1987 Living Stage benefit songs (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Living Stage pieces 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - screenplays descriptions (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 1986-1987 bookings (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Living Stage performances 1969-1981 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - ASP monthly reports 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - mental health evaluations; 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Ballou Evaluations 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Sharpe Evaluations 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Woodson Sr. and Jr. High School evaluations 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Season Evaluations 1981 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - evaluations 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - evaluations 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Washington Free School Evaluations 1985 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Season evaluations 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Jenn evaluations 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - season evaluations 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 1982 youth in arts project (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Living Stage; the improvisational process and the myth of the black underclass (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - OSAP high risk - budget and fact sheets 1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - OSAP budget - teen mom program (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - concept paper for conference OSAP (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - conference support and letters; OSAP (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - OSAP: budget conference (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - OSAP conference grant proposal 1992 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - OPEC; correspondence (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - copies of support letters for high risk youth program; 4/92 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - season archives; 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - ADASA activities reports 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - ADASA 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - public performances; misc. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - workshop flyers; 1992 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - afro-centric workshop; 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Living Stage summer workshop song repertoire (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - proposal to National Black Child Development Institute; 3/20/92 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Princess Grace Foundation proposal; March 1991 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - proposal to the County of Fairfax, Department of Community Action; 12/90 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - budget 1992 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - budget 1991 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - KOBA 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Children First Workshop; sch. and reports, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Living Stage: theater school/actors training program (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - "The Hearts and Minds of Young Mothers" (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - high risk youth prevention grant; 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - teen mothers - Narrative (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - National Museum of American Art; 1996 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - ADASA - official letters/forms (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 1991-1992 major programs paper (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - adopt a visitor program: 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 1993-1994 season summary (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - grant proposals; 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - news releases; misc. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - casting, spring 1994 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - special events; 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - summer workshop market analysis; 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Board Committee notes; 1989-1991 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Board Committee minutes and memos; 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - 1992 fall workshop calender listing and P.S.A. (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Living Stage national Leadership fellow; 8/7/92 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - 1992 late-summer workshop flyers (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - D.C. art works SYEP; 1990 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - general information; Living Stage (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - D.C. art works; 1988 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - TMOT assessment 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Stockholm; May 1990 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - board; 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - communications team 1997-1998 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - board development working group 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Living Stage board book; 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 1999-2000 strategic planning group (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Community Partnership Team (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Communications Partnership team (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Robert Alexander's Vita-Long (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Season Summary 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Conflict Resolution Sheet (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Season Summary: 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - season summaries 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Vanessa's 1991 residency update (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Wendy's 1988 report on the impact of the residencies (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Sample Residency Proposal (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Living Stage performance groups; 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - transcript of Living Stage workshop and interviews with Lillian Barns and Oran Sandel (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Child fest 1994-1996 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Children First program (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - CTNI (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - HASBRO 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Hasbro (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Living Stage and the creative process (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - program fact sheets; 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Workshop Brochures; 1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - press on Living Stage (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Catherine's Testimony 1991; D.C. Commission of the Arts and Humanities (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Summer Youth Employment; 1991 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - remarks by Remi Bosseau and Olympia Dukakis; 4/17/89 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - testimony on ADASA; 7/15/93 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - "Healing our Society through Creativity" (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Vanessa's testimony; D.C. Public Health Commission; 6/15/93 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Catherine's testimony to the DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities; 2/11/93 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - testimonies to committee on human services; 2/19/92 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Catherine's speech to "Join Together Fellows" 8/92 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Temple Award acceptance- June 1992 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - 1991-1992 season evaluation of special products (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - TMOT evaluation - Marty Bayer 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - 1991-1992 season evaluations Jennifer Nelson (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Sharpe Evaluations 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - TMOT evaluations (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Garrison Elementary (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - LORTON (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - I.H.A.D. evaluations 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - CYS (COBS) 1992-1993 evaluations (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Kimball Elementary 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - KOBA 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Sharpe Health 1993-1994 season evaluations (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - LORTON/CTF 1993-1994 Season Evaluations (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - KOBA 1993-1994 season evaluations (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Kimball 1993-1994 season evaluations (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Garrison Elementary 1993-1994 season evaluations (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - teen mothers 1993-1994 season evaluation (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - 1998-1999 evaluations w/ Marty Beyer (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - workshop 1986 general (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - press for workshop 1986 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 1986 workshop budget (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - South Carolina (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - KIDZ BIZ (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - old thank you letters; misc. dates (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Ads for workshops; 1985 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - press for workshops (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - workshop budget 1985 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - workshop summer 1985 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - special targeting 1986 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - ads for workshop 1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - TCG (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Weekend workshop (Box 49, Folder 14)